<odoo>
    <template id="s_eventzo_car_section" name="Eventzo Enquiry Blog Section">
        <section class="s_eventzo_enquiry_section o_cc o_cc1" data-name="Eventzo Enquiry Blog Section">
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row">
                    <!-- Left Column: Blog / Service Content -->
                    <div class="col-lg-8 col-md-12">
                        <h2 class="eventzo_blog_title mb-3">
                            Unforgettable luxury wedding cars for your special day.
                        </h2>

                        <p>
                            Wedding car rental service is a fantastic business.
                            <strong>Eventzo Event Management company</strong>
                            offers the best wedding cars from various cities for your big day.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            The wedding ceremony is a very important event for every person’s life. They want to make their
                            wedding day extra something special and memorable. Nowadays, couples desire to plan every aspect
                            of their wedding, including decorations, makeup, <strong>wedding dance</strong>, entertainment, and DJs.
                            Among these categories, wedding cars are an exceptional addition to each couple’s life.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Make your grand entrance in style with our unforgettable collection of luxury wedding cars.
                            From sleek modern classics to timeless vintage beauties, each vehicle is perfectly
                            maintained to add sophistication and glamour to your special day.
                            Let us turn your wedding journey into an experience as memorable as the ceremony itself.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Your wedding day deserves nothing less than perfection. Our luxury wedding cars offer elegance, comfort, and class — ensuring you
                            arrive with grace and leave with unforgettable memories. Experience the joy of traveling in pure style,
                            making every moment of your big day truly special.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Make a lasting impression on your special day with our premium range of luxury wedding cars.
                            Designed to offer elegance, comfort, and class, our fleet features only the finest vehicles — perfect for
                            couples who desire something truly exceptional.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Each car is carefully detailed and maintained to perfection,
                            ensuring every ride feels as special as the occasion itself. Our courteous chauffeurs deliver a seamless, stress-free experience,
                            arriving on time and dressed with professionalism.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Whether you dream of arriving in a sleek modern sedan or a charming vintage classic,
                            our service guarantees an unforgettable entrance — because you deserve nothing less on your big day.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            The rental price for wedding cars starts at various prices. With this price, you can rent
                            a wedding car for 80 kilometers and 8 hours on your wedding day. If you require more kilometers, an
                            additional 50 rupees will be charged per kilometer. Similarly, if you need more hours, an extra 500 rupees
                            will be added per hour. These are the standard prices for Kerala wedding cars.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            You can choose from various luxury vehicles like Audi, BMW, and Mercedes-Benz in this price range. Another
                            category that many couples love is vintage cars. These vintage cars are available at similar prices.
                        </p>

                        <p>
                            Apart from that, premium wedding luxury cars like Rolls-Royce and Jaguar are also available. While
                            these cars might be more expensive, they are worth considering for their elegance and style. All cars come
                            with experienced drivers and are available in all cities. Our event management planners are
                            ready to assist you with your needs in almost every city. If you want a luxury wedding car for your
                            event day, please contact us as soon as possible.
                        </p>
                    </div>

                    <!-- Right Column: Enquiry Sidebar -->
                    <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-12">
                        <div class="eventzo_enquiry_sidebar">
                            <!-- Top Image Card -->
                            <div class="eventzo_enquiry_image_card mb-3">
                                <img src="/theme_eventzo/static/src/img/venue3.jpeg"
                                     alt="Enquiry Image" class="eventzo_enquiry_img"/>
                                <div class="eventzo_enquiry_overlay">
                                    <img src="/theme_eventzo/static/src/img/header.png"
                                         alt="Eventzo" class="eventzo_logo_white mb-2"/>
                                    <p class="small mb-0">ISO 9001:2015 CERTIFIED COMPANY</p>
                                    <h5 class="mt-2 mb-1 fw-bold">Make an Enquiry!</h5>
<!--                                    <a href="/contact" class="btn eventzo_enquiry_btn">Let's Talk</a>-->
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <!-- Form Card -->
                            <div class="eventzo_enquiry_form_box">
                                <h5 class="eventzo_form_title mb-3">Request quote</h5>
                                <form class="eventzo_enquiry_form">
                                    <div class="mb-3">
                                        <input type="text" class="form-control" placeholder="Enter your Full Name" />
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="mb-3">
                                        <input type="tel" class="form-control" placeholder="Enter your Phone Number" />
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="mb-3">
                                        <input type="email" class="form-control" placeholder="Enter your Email ID" />
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="mb-3">
                                        <textarea class="form-control" rows="4" placeholder="Message"></textarea>
                                    </div>
                                    <button type="submit" class="btn eventzo_submit_btn w-100">SUBMIT</button>
                                </form>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
    </template>
</odoo>
