<!-- templates/parties_content.xml -->
<odoo>
    <template id="s_eventzo_parties_content" name="Eventzo Parties Content">
        <section class="s_eventzo_parties_content pt96 pb96" data-name="Eventzo Parties Content">
            <div class="container">
                <!-- Section Title -->
                <div class="row mb-5">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <h2 class="eventzo_parties_section_title text-center">
                            Explore Exclusive DJ nights,Foam Fusions and More
                        </h2>
                    </div>
                </div>

                <!-- Feature Image -->
                <div>
                    <div>
                        <div class="eventzo_parties_feature_image">
                            <img src="/theme_eventzo/static/src/img/dj.jpg" alt="DJ Party Setup"/>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <br/>

                <!-- Text Content -->
                <div class="row">
                    <div class="col-12">
                        <div class="eventzo_parties_text_content">
                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                Eventzo Event Management provides private party organising services where we specialise
                                in planning and executing events of various types, including private parties.
                            </p>

                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                The services can vary depending on the client's specific needs and requirements of the
                                clients. Some common services offered by us for private parties may include:
                            </p>

                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                <strong>Planning the event:</strong>
                                Our planners provide private party services along with planning and
                                coordination of the entire occasion. We help you in choosing the ideal location,
                                contracting and managing vendors, and take care of inviting the guests and RSVPs.
                                Developing timetables, and other specifics are also taken care of by our managers. They
                                ensure that the event goes smoothly without a hitch and according to schedule.
                            </p>

                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                <strong>Theme development and décor:</strong>
                                Eventzo Event Management Company,work closely with clients to develop a theme
                                for their private party, whether it's a formal affair, a casual get-together, or a
                                themed celebration. We can also help with décor, lighting, and other design elements to
                                create the desired atmosphere.
                            </p>

                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                <strong>Catering:</strong>
                                An important part of any event, we also arrange international and local cuisines,
                                snacks, and even a bar service where required. As we offer a wide range of food and
                                beverage choices, we employ catering professionals help you design a custom menu that
                                meets your guests’ dietary needs and preferences, and can often provide staffing and
                                cleanup services as well.
                            </p>

                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                <strong>Decorations:</strong>
                                Decorations can set the tone for your event and help create a memorable atmosphere. Our
                                private party services can help you choose the right decorations for your theme and
                                venue, and can often provide setup and takedown services as well.
                            </p>

                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                <strong>Rentals:</strong>
                                If you need tables, chairs, linens, or other party supplies, our private party services
                                offer rental options that make it easy and convenient for you to get everything you need
                                in one place. We often deliver and set up your rentals for you, and also provide pickup
                                and cleanup services after your event.
                            </p>

                            <p class="eventzo_parties_paragraph">
                                Reach out to Eventzo Event Management Company,for a variety of private party
                                services to ease your stress. We make organising simpler as we take care of delegating
                                important tasks to the right people so that you can concentrate on having a great time
                                at the event.
                            </p>


                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
    </template>
</odoo>