<odoo>
    <template id="s_eventzo_wedding_service_details" name="Eventzo Wedding Service Details">
        <section class="s_eventzo_wedding_details" data-name="Wedding Service Details">
            <div class="container">
                <div class="eventzo_wedding_content">
                    <p>
                        <em>As a leading wedding</em> event management agency,
                        <strong>Eventzo Event Management</strong>
                        provides a wide range of services:
                    </p>

                    <h4>Design and décor</h4>
                    <p>
                        At every wedding, design and décor are eye-catching elements that breathe life into any bridal occasion.
                        Most destination wedding planners don’t conceptualize or coordinate all parts of the ceremony.
                        But we are different. As one of the top wedding planning companies, we execute a wedding theme fully,
                        with floral arrangements, lighting, props, and other elements according to your small or big requirements and creative vision.
                        We expand our scope to provide décor services as well and engage in extensive brainstorming before demonstrating
                        how a particular idea will meet your expectations.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        We also perform cost calculations and settle for an appropriate theme from all angles.
                        Our in-house <strong>wedding decoration</strong> production makes it easier for us to handle all aspects of planning and execution.
                    </p>

                    <h4>Choosing a venue and a destination</h4>
                    <p>
                        Finding the ideal location for your wedding can be difficult and exhausting.
                        Most <strong>destination wedding</strong> planners don’t do them as well as they should.
                        There are several restrictions that apply to this activity, including time of year, spending limits, and the availability of a venue.
                        With these facts in mind, as one of the best destination wedding planners,
                        <strong>Eventzo Event Management</strong> coordinates with you to identify your dream location.
                        We can make magic anyplace with reasonable <strong>destination wedding packages</strong>,
                        including beaches, backwaters, or the highlands.
                    </p>

                    <h4>Food</h4>
                    <p>
                        Food is common and yet unique. We enjoy savoring various cuisines from across the world and strive to create menus and meal plans that
                        appear beautiful and surprise guests. Therefore, we infuse thoughtful components to make eating extremely interesting.
                        Everything appears to fall into place when the cuisine is tasty and presented well.
                        Food can heavily influence wedding experiences; therefore, we collaborate with best caterers
                        to bring special treats that satisfy your guests’ appetites.
                    </p>

                    <h4>Entertainment</h4>
                    <p>
                        A wedding becomes exciting and beautiful when all your favorite people are invited.
                        Your guests are the life of the ceremony, so we ensure they are thoroughly pleased and entertained.
                        Fun activities are planned for the evening — we could even bring a celebrity performer to dazzle the audience.
                        With our wedding entertainment services, we can bring any of these concepts to life to satisfy your guests fully.
                    </p>

                    <h4>Contact and Communication</h4>
                    <p>
                        Seamless communication is one of the most essential components of a wedding.
                        It takes a little creativity to draft and design wedding invitations that perfectly match the wedding’s theme.
                        Our creative team at Eventzo works closely with you to ensure every element — from design to tone — reflects your unique celebration.
                    </p>

                    <!-- Two side-by-side centered wedding images -->
                    <div class="eventzo_wedding_two_images">
                        <img src="/theme_eventzo/static/src/img/wed_table.jpg"
                             alt=""
                             class="eventzo_two_img"/>
                        <img src="/theme_eventzo/static/src/img/wed_chair.jpg"
                             alt=""
                             class="eventzo_two_img"/>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
    </template>
</odoo>
